helloarticle.com 2014-04-04

# HelloArticle.com

|   | 

**Privacy Policy**  
  
---|---  
  | Thank you for visiting **_HelloArticle.com_**. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using **_HelloArticle.com_** or submitting any personal information. By using **_HelloArticle.com_** , you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.  
  | Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for **_HelloArticle.com_** only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.  

#### Collection of Information  
  
  | We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors and authors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.  
  
#### Cookie/Tracking Technology  
  
  | **_HelloArticle.com_** may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to **_HelloArticle.com_** , and understanding how visitors use **_HelloArticle.com_**. Cookies can also help customize **_HelloArticle.com_** for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.  
  
#### Distribution of Information  
  
  | We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.  
  
#### Commitment to Data Security  
  
  | Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from **_HelloArticle.com_** allow you to opt out of further mailings.   
  
#### The DoubleClick Cookie on the Google content network  
  
  | Google uses the DoubleClick cookie on **_HelloArticle.com_** to help advertisers and publishers serving and managing ads across the web. When you visit a website and view or click on an ad served through **_HelloArticle.com_** , Google may place the DoubleClick cookie on your browser. The DoubleClick cookie identifier associated with your web brower is the same identifier used when you visit websites that use DoubleClick advertising services. If you already have a DoubleClick cookie on your browser, no additional DoubleClick cookies should be dropped. 

For more information about the use of the DoubleClick cookie in DoubleClick’s advertising services, check out the DoubleClick Privacy FAQ ( http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx ). 

You may view and manage your advertising preferences or opt out of receiving the DoubleClick cookie at any time ( http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/ ).  
  
#### Privacy Contact Information  
  
  | If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:  
By e-mail: http://www. ** _HelloArticle.com_**.com/email.htm  
  |    
  | We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.  
  |    
  | Vienna, May 2009
